&gt;&gt; Okay, we are here in the Google Self-Driving Car.
— 现在 我们在 Google 的无人驾驶汽车里
We're inside.
我们就在车里面
It's obviously driving itself.
你可以看到 这辆车自己在行驶
And it's doing everything by itself.
所有操作都是汽车自动执行的
&gt;&gt; And I am here as a passenger.
— 我是这辆车的乘客
I'm really hoping that Sebastian did a good job in training this,
我衷心希望 Sebastian 训练好了这辆车
because he is not driving right now, and I-
因为他现在并没有在操纵方向盘
&gt;&gt; I am not driving, it drives better than me.
— 没错 我并没有在开车 无人驾驶比我更出色
&gt;&gt; I am at the mercy of this car.
— 我的小命完全掌握在这辆车手里
That's true, it does drive better than me.
不过它确实开得比我好 千真万确
&gt;&gt; So why are we talking about self-driving cars then?
— 那么 我们为什么要讨论无人驾驶车呢？
&gt;&gt; Why are we talking about self driving cars?
— 为什么要讨论无人驾驶车？
Well we're going to start by talking about supervised classification, and
我们要从监督学习（分类）说起
self-driving cars are one big supervised classification problem.
无人驾驶汽车是一个重要的监督学习问题
&gt;&gt; What does supervised mean?
— 那么“监督”是什么意思？
&gt;&gt; Supervised means that you have a bunch of examples,
— “监督”表示你有许多不同情况的数据
where you know sort of the correct answer in those examples.
并且你知道这些情况下的正确操作
So I know that you have an example of this from the self-driving cars.
我知道 你有很好的无人驾驶汽车的数据
&gt;&gt; Yeah so I mean we train our car and
— 是的 我们向汽车展示正确的驾驶行为
we show the car what's the right behavior.
来训练汽车
And we did the DARPA Grand Challenge we would take it out for a spin and it would
我们还参加了 DARPA 挑战赛 我们会开着它去兜风
very carefully watch us human drivers drive and would emulate our behavior.
它会仔细观察人类是如何驾驶的 并模拟我们的行为
&gt;&gt; And in fact, this is sort of how people learn to drive, right?
— 实际上这和我们自己学开车有点像 对吗？
&gt;&gt; Yeah, I think so. When I was a child, I watched my parents drive.
— 没错 我小时候会观察父母开车
And they weren't really good drivers, but
虽然他们并不是很优秀的司机
I would still copy a lot of stuff from them.
但我仍然从他们身上模仿了不少开车的技巧
&gt;&gt; Yeah, so it's kind of like,
— 是的 这有点像
in the way the humans drive by watching lots of examples.
人类自身通过观察很多例子来学习开车
That's what computers do when they're doing machine learnings.
计算机进行机器学习时也是如此
You give them lots of examples, and they start to figure out what's going on.
人类提供给它们很多示例 它们自己进行分析
That's what we'll be learning about.
这就是我们要学习的内容
&gt;&gt; And it's totally true.
— 没错
In this unit, you're going to be learning about
在本单元中 你将学习机器学习
machine learning, the same way we program self-driving car.
也就是我们在为无人驾驶车编程的方式
You're going to program data and
你将利用行驶数据进行编程
test out whether you can make a car go fast and slow at the appropriate time.
测试是否可以使用有监督的机器学习
using machine learning supervised learning.
让汽车在适当的时刻进行加速或减速
&gt;&gt; That's right. So
— 没错 所以
we're going to be looking at a really cool terrain classification problem that
我们将分析一个很酷的地形分类问题
was very important for Stanley.
这个问题这对 Stanley 非常重要
You want to introduce that?
你想要介绍这个内容吗？
&gt;&gt; So, in Stanley's case, I was driving through the desert and
— 我开着 Stanley 穿过了沙漠
the desert terrain is like ruts
沙漠的地形起伏不定
and broom and can be very brutal.
坑坑洼洼 路况十分恶劣
So it you drive too fast, you are running the risk of flipping over and
所以如果车速过快
destroying yourself.
就可能因为翻车而出局
So one thing we've trained the car to do is to really slow down at
所以 我们训练无人驾驶车的一个步骤就是
the appropriate time.
让他学会在适当的时候减速
We did this not by writing little rules,
我们不是通过编写简单的规则来实现这一点
we did it by us demonstrating to the car how we drive.
我们向汽车展示人类是如何在这种情况下驾驶的
And it will just emulate us.
它会模仿我们的驾驶方式
&gt;&gt; How many miles did you have to drive to train that.
— 训练这一目标需要行驶多少英里？
&gt;&gt; Oh thousands of miles.
— 哦 我们需要开车几千英里
We spent thousands of miles everyday in the desert.
我们每天都要在沙漠里开上几千英里
&gt;&gt; Wow. &gt;&gt; And it took quite a while for it to become smart.
— 天哪 — 我们花了相当长的时间才让汽车变聪明一些
&gt;&gt; Your poor grad students.
— 可以想象 你的研究生们
I can only imagine.
实在是太可怜了
&gt;&gt; Well, I was the guy who had the pizza for everybody, but, it was a great time
— 我是那个为大家准备披萨的人 那是一段非常美好的时光
because it was no email, we just had the, us and the software.
没有电子邮件 只有我们和软件
And every time you got the software back it was very obvious,
每次软件做的不好时 很明显
the car would punish us.
汽车就会惩罚我们
&gt;&gt; Oh, that sounds great.
— 听起来很棒
So, I think we should probably get started with that.
我们可以从这个例子开始
Let's try out a few different supervised classification problems.
尝试一些不同的监督分类问题
&gt;&gt; Yeah, so the unit's all about supervised learning, so let's dig in.
— 是的 本单元都是关于监督学习的 我们开始吧
&gt;&gt; Sounds great.
— 不错